Guide to the Bernice C. Rowell Photographs
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Bernice C. Rowell photographs
1900-1903
PC0154
Rowell, Bernice C.
105.92 megabyte(s)
(191 computer files)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Collection Contents
- Photographs, 1900-1903
  - The Gates Entrance to Stanford University, 1; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Arches from the Oval, 2; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Arches from Memorial Court, 3; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - West Arch, 4; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - East Arch, 5; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Corridors -A, 6; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Corridors -B, 7; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Untitled (Quad & Arch), 8; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Election Day on the Quad, 9; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Quad, 10; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Library, 11; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Museum, 12; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Church -1, 13; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Church -2, 14; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Church -3, 15; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Coiufr ??, 16; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Encina Hall, 17; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Roble Hall, 18; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona-A, 19; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona-B, 20; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona-C, 21; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona-D, 22; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona-E, 23; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - For the Fancy dress party -A, 24; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - For the Fancy dress party -B, 25; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - For the Fancy dress party -C, 26; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sara Graham Morrison, 1901 -A, 27; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sara Graham Morrison, 1901 -B, 28; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Beach (seven students), 29; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Graduation -A, 30; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Graduation -B, 31; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Decorations in Roble Gym for Madrino Party, 32; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Salvatora Street, 33; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Prof. Strauss ( house), 34; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Zeta Psi House, 35; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Phi Delta House, 36; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Lake Lagunitta, 37; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Boat House on Lake Lagunitta, 38; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The road past Roble Gym, 39; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Roble Gym, 40; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Palo Alto, 41; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Horses of the Stock Farm, 42; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The biggest Pipe of the University, 43; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - A road at the Flood Estate, 44; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Residence of the Flood Estate -A, 45; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Residence of the Flood Estate -B, 46; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - ? Flood Estate or Campus?, 47; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Mausoleum, 48; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Stanford Place -A, 49; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Stanford Place -B, 50; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Tablet Erected, 1898, 51; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Tablet (Obverse), 52; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Campus behind Lake Lag, 53; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - In the Arboritieum, 54; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Rowell Family in Fresno, 55; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Rowell Family in Fresno (Uncle Milo in picture), 56; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Old Bridge, 57; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona Girls, 58; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Mabel Childs, 59; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona -C, 60; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona -D, 61; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona ? -E, 62; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona ? -F, 63; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Woman on Quad?, 64; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Woman and Boy & Basket, 65; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group of Women on Steps, 66; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Chorus Line -A, 67; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Chorus Line -B, 68; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sports-A, 69; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sports-B, 70; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group on Porch -A, 71; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group on Porch -B, 72; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Inner Quad Corridor, 73; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Inner Quad Arches, 74; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Canoe on Lake -A, 75; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Canoe on Lake -B, 76; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Three Women on Rail, 77; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Woman Standing, 78; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Tow Women Seated, 79; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group in Forest, 80; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Seven People on Grass, 81; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Five People in carriage, 82; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group Seated on Porch -A, 83; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Large Group on Porch, 84; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group Seated on Porch -B, 85; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Very Large Group on Porch, 86; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Large Group by Palm, f57; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group by Palm Tree, 88; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Ladies Party -A, 89; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Ladies Party -B, 90; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrona ? two Ladies, 91; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Madrone ? with bike, 92; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Dirt Street & Houses, 93; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - House on Campus?, 94; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Arch from inner Quad -A, 95; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Arch from inner Quad -B, 96; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Normal at San Jose, 97; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Prof. Darfy of the Normal (Mabel McDonald, 01a Rowell, 98; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - A Normal Award, 99; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Out of the Canyon, 100; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - At Alum Rock, 101; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - In the Tank, 102; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Fannie Rosendahl-A, 103; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - In the Glen at Alum Rock, 104; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Fannie Rosendahl-B, 105; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the hillside -Fannie Rosendahl, 106; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Eight People by Fence, 107; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Little Girl, 108; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Gathering of People, 109; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Quad, 110; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Three People in Flowers, 111; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Old Bridge at Olive Springs, 112; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - After the Old Bridge at Olive Springs, 113; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Holister, Bike & two Women, 114; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Dress Making Parlors, Holister, 115; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Yard in Hollister, 116; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Four Women in Yard, Holister, 117; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Covered Walkway, Holister, 118; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Church in Holister, 119; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Gathering in Garden, Holister, 120; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Group Seated in Dirt, Holister, 121; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Goat Island, 122; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sailing Ship, 123; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Warship Philadelphia, 124; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Aboard Warship Iowa, 125; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Examiner Building, Night Illumination in honor of Pres. McKinley May 1901, 126; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Donahue Fountain San Francisco, 127; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Chutes -A, 128; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Chutes -B, 129; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Chutes -C, 130; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Chutes -D, 131; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Berkeley -A, 132; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - At the Presido, 133; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - At the Presido, 134; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Battleship Iowa The Ceremony, 135; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - To Mt. Tamalpais Two people in Carriage, 136; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - To Mt. Tamalpais View down the grade, 137; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Top Mt. Tamalpais -A, 138; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Top Mt. Tamalpais -B, 139; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Bridge at Berkeley, 140; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Under the spreading tree (Berkeley?), 141; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Pacific Grove -A, 142; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Pacific Grove -B, 143; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Loop-A Seventeen Mile Drive, 144; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Loop-B Seventeen Mile Drive, 145; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Beach at Cannel, 146; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Ship at Carmel, 147; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Old Custom House at Cannel, 148; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Cannel Mission, 149; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - John Hopkins Lab, 150; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Del Monte, 151; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Hugh Teris Mansion by the Sea -A, 152; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Hugh Teris Mansion by the Sea -B, 153; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - My Raft (Cannel), 154; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - The Beach (Carmel), 155; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Beach (Cannel) -A, 156; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Beach (Cannel) -B, 157; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - On the Beach (Cannel) -C, 158; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Just After Dinner, 159; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Family Photo?, 160; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Fresno, 4th of July, 161; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Courthouse in Fresno, 162; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - View from Courthouse looking down Mariposa St., 163; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - High view of Fresno, 164; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Sign for '06, 165; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Row on Campus?, 166; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Church, 167; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Inner Quad, 168; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Railroad Station? (PA), 169; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Memorial Church Scaffolding, 170; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Chemistry Building, 171; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Chemistry Building & Oval ?, 172; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Campus View (long range), 173; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Graduates -A, 174; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Graduates -B, 175; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Grandmother on Horse with cartridge belt and pistol, 176; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Great Grandparents Rowell (s) on the left, 177; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Great Grandmother Rowell on the left, 178; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Great Grandmother Rowell (middle), 179; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Great Grandmother Rowell (right), 180; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Room 12 1900-1901 (out of order), 181; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Room 1900-1901 (out of order), 182; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)
  - Page with Miss Bernice C. Rowell from the 1904 Junior Class In The Quad, 1904 Vol. X and signed May 13, 1903, Rowellaa.JPG; 1 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Page with Miss Bernice C. Rowell from the 1904 Junior Class In The Quad, 1904 Vol. X and signed May 13, 1903, Rowella.PSD; 1 computer file(s) (PSD)
  - Only Miss Bernice C. Rowell from the 1904 Junior Class In The Quad, 1904 Vol. X and signed May 13, 1903, Rowellbb.JPG; 1 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Only Miss Bernice C. Rowell from the 1904 Junior Class In The Quad, 1904 Vol. X and signed May 13, 1903, Rowellb.PSD; 1 computer file(s) (PSD)
  - Grandparents Arthur & Bernice Rowell Dahlgren's Home in Fresno, California. Home built by Greatgrandfather Rowell (Grandmother's father.)3, Fresnol53EffieStreetjpg; 1 computer file(s) (TIFF)